woah uh woah woah woah
SHINING SOMER DIA
Come on!
Yujio, calm down.
When I count three, we'll charge
past the four guys coming,
and knock out their fires.
Okay.
You can use that thing for light.
When the fires go out,
find a sword and grab it.
Leave the big guy to me.
He won't go down easy, so
keep the others off my back.
But I...
I never fought with a sword before.
Swing it like your axe.
Come on.
One, two, three!
Yu-Gi-Oh!
Yushu!
Don't think!
Just start swinging!
He makes it sound so easy.
It's the light they're
afraid of the light.
I
am
the great
Ugachi the lizard
killer you dare challenge me?
I'm not just gonna challenge
you, I'll kill you!
Sword skill.
Sharp nail!
Kirito!
God!
VR never hurt like this!
You rotten little idiot, you brat!
Take my arm, save me!
You pay in blood!
I'll rip you in half.
Eat your guts.
Cheats you less than insane.
I'm scared.
What?
I can't just stand here.
I can't make the same
mistake I made with Alice.
Die!
I...
DETAIL!
It's time!
I'll fight!
And protect my friends!
Run, Yu-Gi-Oh!
Yu-Gi-Oh!
Hang on, Yu-Gi-Oh! Please!
We made a promise.
You, me, and Alice.
Yes, we promised we'd protect each other.
I couldn't six years ago, but now,
finally, I got to.
That's right.
I couldn't either.
Your turn now.
Now you die!
I'm presenting who you are!
My name's Kirito.
Kitty tell the swordsman!
Either way, you die!
Maybe he's a Flux Blight,
like everyone else.
Still!
If I don't kill him, he'll kill us!
Sword skill!
Sonic! Leave!
Fight's over.
Your boss is dead.
You want to die the
same way, then step up.
But if you want to live, then
go back to the Dark Territory!
Hang in there.
Selka!
Come on, wake up!
Kirito, what are you doing here?
We came to take you back home.
Can you walk okay? In a bit.
My legs are numb and...
Hey, put me down!
Yuji-Oh needs you.
He's hurt bad. He's dying!
My secret art skills aren't enough.
The wound is much too deep.
But you can at least try.
You're Alice's sister.
You can do this.
All I can heal are simple scratches.
If Alice were here, she could
help him more than I could.
Look, you Geo's hurt because he
came to save you, Selka, not Alice.
He's here because of you.
The usual healing arts
would take too long.
I'll have to try a dangerous
high-level one instead.
Kirito, I'm going to need
your help to make this work.
Okay, you got it. What do I do?
Give me your left hand.
I've never done this before.
And if I fail, there's a
chance both of us will die.
I just want you to know that.
If that happens, make
sure it only kills me.
Let's do this.
Mm-hmm.
System call.
Transfer human unit durability.
Right hand to left.
She's transferring her
life and mine to him.
Kirito, can you keep going?
I'm okay.
Hey, don't stop.
Give him more.
Kirito, Eugeo, come and find me.
I am waiting.
At the top of the central cathedral.
I will wait there for you both.
Who was that?
Kirito!
Fifty!
How's your wound doing?
Better? Much better.
All I needed was a day's
rest, and it's almost...
I've been wanting to ask you
about something you said.
Back in the cave, right
before you passed out?
I don't know if you remember,
but it sounded like you thought you,
Alice, and me were friends before.
Yes, I remember.
But we only just met, so I don't
know where all that came from.
It's like, at that moment, I
could see it as clear as day.
You, Alice, and me.
We were born on the same day
and grew up together here.
We were even together the
day Alice was taken away.
That's weird.
By the way, when Selka was healing
you, you didn't happen to hear,
like, a voice, did you?
No, I was totally unconscious,
so I didn't hear a thing. Why?
Did you hear a voice?
I guess I dreamed it.
Forget I asked.
Oh, well.
Time to get to work.
Right. Here you go.
I'm gonna use this.
Wait, you can, you can wield the sword?
You might want to stand back.
Because of that fight
with the goblins, now,
my object control authority
is higher than the swords.
Here goes.
AHHHHHHHHH!
Nice!
I bet you can swing it just as easy.
Kirito, will you...
Will you teach me to use a sword?
If so, I can go get Alice back.
Yujiro.
Alice and her family
have suffered so much.
All because of me.
I couldn't save her.
I don't know why, but I couldn't.
And for the past six years, I
never stopped regretting it.
I want to become strong.
So I can fight.
So I can keep from
making the same mistake.
So I can get back what I lost years ago.
That's why.
That's why I want to become a swordsman.
All right, then. You're on.
I'll teach you everything I know.
The training's going to be tough, though.
That's what I'm hoping.
Before we start, do you remember
what your sword style is called?
Yeah, I remember.
It's the Aincrad style.
All right, Eugeo. Finish it.
Hey, look it!
This is like a dream.
I never thought this day would come.
I didn't believe in
destiny before, but now...
Kirito, my calling wasn't my destiny.
For the past six years, I've
been waiting for you to come!
Yeah, maybe you were.
But then again, maybe I woke up
here just so I could meet you?
Why are you here alone?
Oh, Eugio's with your dad
somewhere, talking about stuff.
Oh, I see.
I'm sure he's getting
a lot of well-deserved
praise for chopping down the demon tree.
After all the effort he
put in, he deserves it.
I decided to study harder so I can be as
good at the sacred arts as my sister was.
Not so I can be like her, mind you.
I wasn't trying to copy
her by going to the cave.
I would never cross
into the dark territory.
But I thought by taking the same path
she did, I'd get closer to her, somehow.
I wanted to go in as far as I could.
In a way,
I guess the whole point
of going there was to
prove to myself I could
never take her place.
No, but you're still amazing.
Me?
What other girl here could walk
into that dark cave all by herself?
I mean, that's something
only you could do.
Only I could do?
What do you mean by that?
You're you, not Alice's replacement.
And you got skills no one else here has.
With a little practice,
you'll master them.
May I have your attention, please?
The greatest wish of Rulet's
founders has been fulfilled.
The demon tree has been felled at last.
So let us all give thanks
to Eugeo, son of Oryx.
According to the law,
when one finishes their calling,
they have earned the right to choose
what their next calling will be.
Go ahead, Eugeo.
Make your choice.
I shall
train
hard and
journey to Senator.
Uh, Eugeo, what could you possibly...
No, I won't question you.
It is your church-given right
to choose your next calling.
As Rulet's elder, I approve
Eugeo's new calling as swordsman!
Selka.
Eugeo.
Before I go, I wanted
to tell you something.
Oh?
What is it?
My goal is to go to Senator
and bring Alice back here.
I thought so.
For the past six years, it's
all I've been thinking about.
But with my calling, I had
no idea how I'd go about it.
Then Kirito suddenly showed up,
and bringing Alice back
didn't seem hopeless anymore.
For some reason, I feel like I
can do anything with him around.
You and your family have suffered
so much, all on account of me.
So, I'll bring Alice back
and make things right.
Have faith in me, and wait for our return.
Well, I can't stop you,
but if you insist… I do.
Okay, I shall wait.
Just make sure the three of you come back.
I'll make sure we all come back safe.
Promise.
Good luck!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
No worries.
Well then, are you ready?
Uh-huh.
I wonder what Central will be like.
Who knows?
It's gotta be way bigger
than Rulid, right?
I certainly hope so.
It looks like rain's coming.
We should hurry before
we get caught in it.
What's wrong?
Huh? What?
Never mind. Shall we go?
Yeah.
Let's do it.
I'm not sure if you want
to keep me in the same way.
I'm not sure if I want you.
I'm still not sure if I want you.
I'm not sure
if I want you.
Next time, Ocean Turtle.
You